Today, we'll discuss the ICICI Lombard Health
Advantage Plan. It's a health
insurance plan that takes into account the healthcare needs of you and your family.
So, first, what is the ICICI Lombard Health
Advantage Plan? It's a
comprehensive health insurance plan that
comes with numerous features that
provide protection for you and your family. It includes everything from
restoration
benefits to cumulative bonuses, health
rewards, domestic air ambulance, newborn
and vaccine cover, maternity cover, PD cover,
personal accident cover, and many more.
Sum insured options: This plan
offers multiple sum assured options
and additional cover against 20 critical illnesses, including
cancer. Furthermore,
it
offers wellness programs that allow you to earn
rewards by adopting healthy habits. The
ICICI Lombard
Health Advantage Plan is an all-around
health care solution designed to protect you and your family.  This
helps you to
know more about this plan, watch this video
completely. Let's start this video
Hello and Namaste Policy Ek Welcome Youtu
Insurance Ki Baat Policy Eks
[Music]
Next we will talk about the
eligibility criteria of this plan, plan benefits
and what is covered in this plan
and what is not covered, so first let's
start with the eligibility criteria
Entry Age The minimum entry age in this plan
is 18 years and maximum 65 years and the
age of the child can be 91 days and
maximum 25 years After this your policy will be
separated Sum Insured
You can choose the sum insured amount from Rs 5 lakh to Rs
3 crore as per your requirement
Plan Type In this you will
get both individual and family floater options
Policy Term Talking about the policy term,
you can choose the option of one, two or three years
Initial Waiting Period The
initial waiting period in this plan is 30
days which is applicable for all  The plan itself is the same.
Now let's discuss
some of the key benefits of the ICICI Lord Health Advantage plan.
This is a health
insurance plan that
offers flexibility, and you
can customize the plan to suit your needs.
Wellness and Value-Added Services:
First, let's talk about wellness and value-added
services. In this plan, you get
wellness rewards such as health rewards,
medical condition management programs, video
teleconsultation, telemedicine, pharmacy and
diagnostic services, online chat with a
doctor, doctor on call, and discounts on health assistance
services. Then comes
Worldwide Cover. The ICICI Lord Health Advantage plan offers
worldwide cover.
This includes hospitalization expenses
outside India, USA, and Canada. This is a
comprehensive facility and
covers a specified amount, as
mentioned in the policy schedule. Home care treatment is
another key benefit of this plan.
If you are on home care treatment, the
ICICI Lord Health Advantage plan will
cover you for a maximum of up to 5,000 patients.  Of the sub-
insured or maximum up to Rs. 255,000
Tax benefits as per certain terms and conditions
And finally, we talk about
tax benefits. All premium payments of this plan are
tax-
free under the Income Tax Act of India.
ICICI Lord Health Advantage
plan is a very versatile and
comprehensive health insurance plan. You
get not only health cover but also
many other additional benefits. Now let's talk about
what is covered in this plan.
Room rent:
From private single AC room to
twin sharing and general suite, everything is covered in the IIID Health Advantage plan up
to the sum assured ICU charges: ICU
charges are covered up to the sum assured Pre
and post hospitalization: Pre-
hospitalization is covered up to 60 days and
post-hospitalization is covered up to 180 days Domicile
hospitalization i.e. home hospitalization.
If you cannot go to the hospital and
want to get treatment at home or
in a bed in the hospital, this plan covers
Covers up to sum in short, but
remember the hospitalization should be 72 hours or
more Day care treatment
Treatments that can be treated in less than
24 hours of hospitalization like blood
dialysis Cataract etc. are covered up to
sum in short No Claim Bonus This plan offers you a
no claim bonus of up to 100% of
the sum insured for every claim-free year
Automatic Restoration This plan
offers you automatic restoration of 100% of
your sum insured Daily Hospital Cash Daily
hospital cash is covered in this plan The
covered amount is dependent on your selected
sum assured Organ Donor Organ donor
expenses are also covered up to the sum assured
Maternity Cover
Maternity cover is an optional benefit in ICICI Health Advantage plan
which covers up to 10% of your base sum assured
but the maximum
limit is under Rs. 10 lakh. So
if good news is about to come in your family, then
this  The plan can be very beneficial
and can be customized to suit your needs.
What is Newborn Baby Cover? Newborn baby cover
covers medical expenses related to hospitalization of a newborn baby,
especially in unforced circumstances.
It includes some common treatments like
congestive heart failure, anemia, sinusitis, birth defects, acute conditions,
chronic conditions, premature delivery, birth
asphyxia, and day care treatments. There
may be slight variations from plan to plan.
Newborn baby cover is available in this plan,
which is for a newly born child up to the cover limit.
It comes as an optional cover over and above the maternity limit. So,
if you are expecting a
new member in your family, it can be a
good feature. Always great to have
the extra layer of protection. AYUSH
treatment: It provides you with alternative
treatments like AYUSH treatment up to the sum
insured. Ambulance charges are covered
up to the sum insured. Air
ambulance is covered up to Rs 5 lakh under this
plan. Global coverage  This means
you are outside India and face any medical
emergency.
Global coverage in the ICICI Health Advantage plan is for those
who opt for a sub-insurance of ₹25 lakh and above.
This will provide
coverage for worldwide medical emergencies, but this
facility will be available only to those who choose high sub-
insured options. Health
checkup: Under this facility, policyholders
can avail free health checkups after completing the company's policies.
One health checkup is available every year,
starting from the first year of the policy.
Under this benefit, you can avail health checkups up to 0.5 of the sum insured or a
maximum of ₹10,000
on a cashless basis. E-consultation: E-
consultation means you can connect with a doctor online for
consultation
through video chat, audio call, or chat.
Vaccination cover: Vaccination cover means
that if you or a family member incurs
vaccination expenses, the
insurance company will cover that expense.
Now, ICICI Lombard Health
What is its status in the Advantage Plan? This
plan covers vaccination expenses
up to 1 per cent of the base sum insured per
newborn child. Maximum co-payment up to 10,000.
Let's talk
about co-payment. This plan has co-payment
clauses, which are very important to know. Co-
payment means that when
hospitalization expenses are incurred, the
policyholder has to pay a portion,
and the rest will be paid by the insurance company.
In the ICICI Lombard Health Advantage Plan, you get a choice. You have to choose whether
you want to pay 10 per cent or 20 per cent.
Now let's talk about the permanent exclusions of this plan,
which
include coverage against Acquired Immune
Defense Syndrome (AIDS), Investigation
and Evaluation, Rest Cure, Rehabilitation and
Response Care, Obesity, Weight Control,
Changes of Gender Treatment, Cosmetic and
Plastic Surgery, Hazards and Adventure
Sports, Breach of Law. All these things are
not covered in this plan. If you
want to take this plan,  If yes, then you
can visit our PolicyX website, the
link of which you will
find in the description box or you
can talk to our expert advisor which is absolutely
free of cost, they will help you
in choosing the right plan and if you found this video
informative then you can like us,
share it, comment on it
and do not
forget to subscribe, so with this we will meet
in the next video till then happy and sharing